<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">



  

<title type="text">Dads Gaming</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.dadsgaming.com/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.dadsgaming.com/" />
<updated>2014-07-29T12:37:28-07:00</updated>
<id>http://www.dadsgaming.com/</id>
<author>
  <name>Dads Gaming</name>
  <uri>http://www.dadsgaming.com/</uri>
  <email>you@email.com</email>
</author>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Borderlands 2 on PS Vita - A Gigantic, Overly Criticized World ]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.dadsgaming.com/reviews/borderlands-2-on-ps-vita-a-gigantic-overly-criticized-world/"/>
  <id>http://www.dadsgaming.com/reviews/borderlands-2-on-ps-vita-a-gigantic-overly-criticized-world</id>
  <updated>2014-07-29 12:47:00 -0700T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2014-07-29T00:00:00-07:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Dads Gaming</name>
    <uri>http://www.dadsgaming.com</uri>
    <email>you@email.com</email>
  </author>
  <category scheme="http://www.dadsgaming.com/tags/#PS%20Vita" term="PS Vita" /><category scheme="http://www.dadsgaming.com/tags/#Reviews" term="Reviews" />
  <content type="html">
  
    &lt;p&gt;There aren’t many things I adore more in life than filling Bandits with so many bullets that they explode, hunting down rare loot chests, or taking down Raid Bosses.  Well… there is one thing I love more,  the ability to do this on my couch while my wife is trying to kill me by watching The Bachelorette for 3 hours.  Borderlands 2 on the PS Vita a little gift from above that helps me retain my sanity in these troubling times known as “compromise”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On that note… I’ll admit it right off the bat, I was skeptical of Borderlands 2 on the Playstation Vita.  When it launched back on May 13th of this year, I couldn’t give myself one good reason to shell out 39.99 for a game I had played for countless hours on my Xbox 360.  Let’s face the fact that Playstation launched this game with a bullet in its leg and pushed it out the door to get beat mercilessly to death by critics.  There was virtually no advertisement for the game other than a Gamestop Vita Bundle, they pulled 4 player co-op from the game within a few weeks of launch, and news was circling that Sony was not creating first party content for the handheld anymore.  It looked like Borderlands 2 was going to be fighting an uphill battle to gain any good attention from the media and gamers alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Borderlands 2 is a great game, full stop. But very little of what’s made it a blast to play over the last couple of years hasn’t been poisoned by this version’s technical issues. Its compromised visuals rob it of much of its bombastic charm, while its erratic performance and unreliable touch controls keep the gameplay from shining like it has in the past.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be fair, that review was also before numerous updates and fixes have been applied so the harshness was probably legit for the time.  A quick search on Google will land you many similar reviews from that time, and the fact is that many were not pretty. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not here to sell you on the PS Vita, hell I can barely sell myself on the system and I have owned it since it launched back in 2012. If you’re considering buying a Vita at this point I will fully recommend this game as one of your first purchases.  As I stated earlier, I couldn’t justify pulling the trigger and buying Borderlands for my Vita.  Summer was rolling along just fine for me in regards to gaming and my fall was looking like it wasn’t going to slow down, but then I realized something.  I was going to be a dad sooner rather than later, in fact my wife is due to deliver here any day now.  Solo TV team was going to change for me drastically.  This prompted me to move in a different direction with my gaming habits, it was time to leave the safety of my Xbox One.  I began purchasing games via Steam, Nintendo 3DS, and on my PS4 (for remote play) and Vita. So there I was, sitting and planning (or scheming as my wife referred to it) on how I was going to get my gaming fix in and it hit me. I NEEDED Borderlands 2 back in my life. #Triggerpulled&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the game finally loaded up for me and I once again put my boots back onto the icy shores of Pandora I wasn’t initially impressed.  The reviews I had read prior to going back in really had made me jaded about the upcoming experience. I was constantly scrutinizing every little detail, like i knew what it would have taken to make the game better.  It wasn’t until I laughed out loud when Claptrap started going through his normal insane babbling that I truly realized what I was REALLY doing.  I was playing fucking Borderlands 2 on a handheld fucking system.  Albeit, the games graphic surely took a hit, the number of enemies on the screen were decreased, and ragdoll effects were completely removed.  But in the grand scheme of things how can anyone complain?  For the 40.00 price tag (You know, the cost of a terrible Xbox One or PS4 game) you are getting one of the best games of 2012 on the go.  The game comes packed with all the DLC and characters as well, and with me not finishing all the DLC for Borderlands when I was playing it on 360 this made the deal even sweeter .  Here’s a list of awesome for you, in case you forgot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Torgue’s Campaign of Carnage Add On Campaign - Explosions!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Captain Scarlett and Her Pirate’s Booty Add On Campaign - Booty!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Psycho Character Class - Kreig!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mechromancer Character Class - Gaige!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the major focal points of most reviews you read is the control set-up.  To be honest, they are not the best controls you could ask for, but they are far from broken.  Running is executed by tapping the left rear touchpad, melee is the right side, grenades are lower right front screen, and your Vault Hunter’s Special Ability is activated on the left of the front screen. None are ideal, none are game breakers, if anyone tells you otherwise they are really nitpicking the issue. The only real complaint I could see is hand cramping, but thats just based on the Vita itself, its not exactly and Xbox one controller afterall.  Every other game mechanic works just fine and it really should be an adapt and overcome situation as opposed to a deal breaker. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, if you have played Borderlands 2 you know there is no way I have finished the game and all of its DLC on Vita yet, but I can tell you what I have experienced so far is a refreshing, nostalgic, and sometimes graphically challenged stroll down Xbox 360 memory lane.  Borderlands 2 on PS Vita is a technological feat, Its not a perfect game by any means but it does what games are supposed to do, entertain. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4 Chemical Vials Out of 5 &lt;/p&gt;

  
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dadsgaming.com/reviews/borderlands-2-on-ps-vita-a-gigantic-overly-criticized-world/&quot;&gt;Borderlands 2 on PS Vita - A Gigantic, Overly Criticized World &lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Dads Gaming at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dadsgaming.com&quot;&gt;Dads Gaming&lt;/a&gt; on July 29, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[August Update Xbox One]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.dadsgaming.com/articles/august_update_xbox_one/"/>
  <id>http://www.dadsgaming.com/articles/august_update_xbox_one</id>
  <updated>2014-07-28 12:47:00 -0700T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2014-07-28T00:00:00-07:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Dads Gaming</name>
    <uri>http://www.dadsgaming.com</uri>
    <email>you@email.com</email>
  </author>
  <category scheme="http://www.dadsgaming.com/tags/#XboxOne" term="XboxOne" /><category scheme="http://www.dadsgaming.com/tags/#Articles" term="Articles" />
  <content type="html">
  
    &lt;p&gt;Here’s what’s coming in the August 2014 update:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Low Battery Notifications&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile purchase&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Notifications&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Last Time Seen Online&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your Friends screen will now show the games that are most popular amongst your friends right now&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3D Blu-Ray support&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;OneGuide (Microsoft’s live TV guide thing) support in Brazil, Mexico, Ireland, and Austria&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/ovHyso_jy24&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

  
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dadsgaming.com/articles/august_update_xbox_one/&quot;&gt;August Update Xbox One&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Dads Gaming at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dadsgaming.com&quot;&gt;Dads Gaming&lt;/a&gt; on July 28, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>

</feed>
