<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-27T07:34:40-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Dads Gaming</title><subtitle>Community for Dads Gaming</subtitle><entry><title type="html">What we played in January</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2020/01/27/what-we-played-in-january/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What we played in January" /><published>2020-01-27T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2020/01/27/what-we-played-in-january</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2020/01/27/what-we-played-in-january/">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our first Dads Gaming “What we played”, a new monthly segment where we share what our community has been playing. This month we got a special treat in Rainbow Six Siege, explored Aurora Island in Ghost Recon Breakpoint, dived into Season 3 of Apex Legends, spoiled by the guns in the King of Looter Shooters: Borderlands 3, and cross-played in Call of Duty Modern Warfare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rainbow-six-siege&quot;&gt;Rainbow Six Siege&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/img/post/2020-01-27-rainbow-six-siege.png&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;445&quot; alt=&quot;rainbow-six-siege&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;bypostauthor&quot;&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/img/member/renovatio_42.jpg&quot; class=&quot;avatar &quot; height=&quot;100&quot; width=&quot;100&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author-box-title&quot;&gt; Authored By &lt;a href=&quot;/author/renovatio_42&quot; rel=&quot;author&quot;&gt;renovatio_42&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author_social&quot;&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 15th, 2020 started a five-week celebration for the SIX INVITATIONAL, the premier esports tournament for Rainbow Six Siege. The first Battle Pass dropped, creating a new way to earn rewards: renown boosters, weapon charms, skins for operators and weapons, and more. The Road to S.I. 2020 Battle Pass is available with one &lt;em&gt;Free&lt;/em&gt; track and one &lt;em&gt;Premium&lt;/em&gt; track. If you decide to go the paid track, the proceeds will go to the prize pool for the Six Invitational and other official Rainbow Six esports. Additionally, rewards are given at each and every tier unlock on the paid premium track. There are 35 tiers in all for this event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the weekend of the 18th, a new Stadium map was introduced programs, according to Ubisoft, only for a limited time. The map was a blend of maps we’ve played before, made a new way with bullet-proof glass while the map sat in the middle of a Stadium arena. The map Stadium also gives players &lt;em&gt;all access&lt;/em&gt; to all of the game’s Operators whether you have them unlocked or not. The game type Unranked Bomb where each team takes turns defending or disarming a bomb site. Thursday through Monday every weekend during this limited time is when the Stadium is available. Be sure to link your Ubisoft Club account to your game profile so you’ll receive all the free: gear, renown, and battle points after completing the challenges or participating in the Community Challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JvxnlR1BaEU&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Stadium map has to be one of my all-time favorites! It sits in the center of the ruins of a modern coliseum in Greece and is set for the sole purpose of training/proving grounds for the Operators. In the infield, sits the playable map that has large bulletproof glass exposing one side the building, all within a Kill House made up of the room with little furniture and minimal decorations. Even the plywood walls have &lt;em&gt;“Rainbow Six RnD”&lt;/em&gt; printed on it. The Stadium map has callbacks to the great maps like old Hereford Base, Oregon, and Kanal sharing of the same assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is nothing like Rainbow Six Siege matches, a tense multiplayer focusing on tactics and teamwork. Playing regularly with Dads is a great social experience, with building bonds and improving skills. Every new online match feels refreshing like Chess - where no two matches are ever exactly the same. With environmental destruction, it can create a new path leading to different routes for pursuing or escaping. No other game encourages close-quarters combat, and players who died cannot respawn until the end of around. Even while waiting for the next match, deceased players can observe cameras on the map and provide key intel to active players on their team through callouts or “pings”. Rainbow Six Siege provides escapism that’s unmatched.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ghost-recon-breakpoint&quot;&gt;Ghost Recon Breakpoint&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/img/post/2020-01-27-ghost-recon-breakpoint.png&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;445&quot; alt=&quot;ghost-recon-breakpoint&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;bypostauthor&quot;&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/img/member/macsnig.jpg&quot; class=&quot;avatar &quot; height=&quot;100&quot; width=&quot;100&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author-box-title&quot;&gt; Authored By &lt;a href=&quot;/author/MacSnig&quot; rel=&quot;author&quot;&gt;MacSnig&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author_social&quot;&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ubisoft released their latest Ghost Recon edition with Breakpoint and we’re having a lot of fun running, flying, driving and boating around the archipelago of Auroa and accomplishing our missions. This go-around has us playing as the hero Nomad and taking on our old friend from Wildlands, Colonel Walker (played by Jon Bernthal) and his private army he calls the Wolves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game is really quite beautiful and Ubisoft is continuously seeking feedback from the player community to improve the things we want and squash the bugs that we run into. From the top of mountains overlooking the entire archipelago to submarine bases, the team did a superb job of creating an immersive environment that it is easy to get lost in, especially if you’re playing with no HUD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NREo4k3MHow&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come join us for some friendly fun and casual Wolf and drone killing on any platform of your choice. We have Dad’s playing across PC, Xbox, and PS4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;amzn-assoc-ad-46abd4cb-83f1-4606-a565-4bb57111133c&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//z-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/onejs?MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;adInstanceId=46abd4cb-83f1-4606-a565-4bb57111133c&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;apex-legends&quot;&gt;Apex Legends&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/img/post/2020-01-27-apex-legends.png&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;445&quot; alt=&quot;apex-legends&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;bypostauthor&quot;&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/img/member/basicide.jpg&quot; class=&quot;avatar &quot; height=&quot;100&quot; width=&quot;100&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author-box-title&quot;&gt; Authored By &lt;a href=&quot;/author/basicide&quot; rel=&quot;author&quot;&gt;basicide&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author_social&quot;&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we come to the end of January, Apex Legends is wrapping up Season 3, which saw some of the biggest changes since the initial release of the game, the most prominent being the brand new map, World’s Edge. Featuring a wide variety of environments, the new map has offered exciting challenges to both new and returning players. The other major change was the addition of the 11th Legend, Crypto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crypto brought a second Recon class Legend to the roster. His abilities are focused on surveilling enemy teams with the assistance of his remotely controlled drone. Enemies within 30m of the drone are highlighted with a bright orange triangular ping that tracks the target while they are within this range, and are visible to all teammates. His ultimate ability is an EMP that is triggered by the drone and does 50 damage to all enemy shields within a very large radius, as well as slowing them temporarily. Additionally, it disables enemy Wattson traps, Caustic traps, and Octane jump pads. While he is not the strongest choice in the early game, during the final circles, his ability to pinpoint enemy teams gives you a strong tactical advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, Season 3 has provided a breath of fresh air to the game. The meta of the game has shifted to favor more mid to long-range engagements thanks to larger overall map size and long sightlines. An early complaint of low loot distribution compared to map size has seen some improvement as Respawn has increased the number of loot bins present in many areas. Furthermore, the inclusion of three high tier loot vaults that can be unlocked with special keys has created a tactical tradeoff between getting to a vault quickly versus potentially running into other teams seeking the same thing or waiting in ambush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/C3q_SibAOc4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apex Legends is currently in the middle of a new Limited Time Mode called the Grand Soiree.  This mode has been an arcade-style mashup of 7 game types, each lasting two days. These game types have brought new and exciting twists on the standard game format, including a 3rd person mode, a mode that automatically respawns teammates whenever a ring closes, and a ring that deals high damage and never stops closing. With 3 modes left to go until the event’s conclusion on January 28th, there is still lots of fun to be had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Respawn is quickly approaching the 1st anniversary of Apex Legends, coming up on February 4th, which will coincide with the end of Season 3. No one knows for sure what Respawn has planned to celebrate this momentous occasion, but everyone is excited to see what’s in store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;borderlands-3&quot;&gt;Borderlands 3&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/img/post/2020-01-27-borderlands_3.png&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;445&quot; alt=&quot;borderlands_3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;bypostauthor&quot;&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/img/member/Sacside.jpg&quot; class=&quot;avatar &quot; height=&quot;100&quot; width=&quot;100&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author-box-title&quot;&gt; Authored By &lt;a href=&quot;/author/Sacside&quot; rel=&quot;author&quot;&gt;Sacside&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author_social&quot;&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are carrying a torch for any of the previous versions of Borderlands, then the fire will keep burning for this installment. The guns are the main attraction and the potential of getting a better one is around every corner. Well, at least until about halfway through your first run of the campaign. At some point, you become the angel of death and everyone else is just fodder. And then the fun starts… True Vault Hunter Mode! No explanation needed just turn it on and start, now your playing Borderlands 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gearbox is a seasoned developer any complaints I have about Borderlands 3 can be chalked up to preference and opinion. I am not a fan of open-world games moving towards this new open segment or area model. Borderlands 3 using plants as their open areas (as does outer worlds). It creates unnecessary loads times and UI navigations issues. Even more importantly I love games that have the “if you see it you can go to it” sense of adventure connected to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/MumvhK-ec-c&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Borderlands 3 is still king of the Looter Shooters in my near-sighted eyes. Great guns, great voice actors with Borderlands gameplay. The game should experience an injection of excitement soon with the upcoming release of Takedown at Maliwan’s Blacksite DLC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2019&quot;&gt;Call of Duty: Modern Warfare (2019)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/img/post/2020-01-27-cod-mw.png&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;445&quot; alt=&quot;call-of-duty-modern-warfare&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;bypostauthor&quot;&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/img/member/disarange80.jpg&quot; class=&quot;avatar &quot; height=&quot;100&quot; width=&quot;100&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author-box-title&quot;&gt; Authored By &lt;a href=&quot;/author/disarange80&quot; rel=&quot;author&quot;&gt;disarange80&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;author_social&quot;&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world of remakes, retelling, and reboots of movies, games are no different and this year’s installment of Call of Duty followed suite with Advanced Warfare. I know at first it seemed they ran out of ideas and just wanted to make a quick yearly installment but in my opinion, they did a great job and this is one of the best ones since Modern Warfare 2. With the closing of Season 1 right around the corner, February 11th I wanted to give some thoughts and personal opinions on this year’s installment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I like, the fact that it is grounded, there is no wall jumping, double jumping, grappling hook or jet back. I know a lot of people liked those features but I like the boots on the ground feel and sure there are some people jumping, shooting and laying down all at the same time but there are not as many as there used to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cross-Play and Skilled Based Matchmaking (I know most hate it), the cross-play makes it so there are a lot more people to play with and with the SBMM you play against people that are generally the same skills as you. Very rarely do I have to wait more than a couple of minutes to find a match (not counting loading times) and I have not tried to turn Cross Playoff to see how long it would take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6-0jkgvdrfs&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DLC, the fact that all maps, new guns, and game modes are free is a huge plus for me. I am on a budget and can’t buy a ton of video game-related things so having free DLC is a great feature. Sure there is a store but everything is cosmetic within the store and it will not give you a leg over the competition. The Battle Pass is also all cosmetic so if you want to go for it, most people had enough COD points just from buying the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure there are some negative sides to all of this, for example, a lot of players do not like the SBMM because they didn’t get to play against their Christmas Noobs but I have been on the receiving end of that and more power to Activision for not messing with it. Sure there are bugs, looking at your collision but they are doing weekly updates which include bug fixes and weekly game mode rotation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I feel this is a great installment and the game has a lot to offer, there is still a Battle Royal mode coming out for it which will offer its own take on the mode, more classic and new maps, more guns, more season, and much more. I am looking forward to seeing what else the game as to offer and what it will bring to the table to keep it fresh. I played the single-player and can see it’s fun, I beat it and not really a single-player FPS guy so not much to say about it, as for the coop, that’s hard as heck and need to the premade team for it. I haven’t played much if it but will mess with it one of these days.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>renovatio_42</name></author><category term="[&quot;games&quot;]" /><category term="xbox" /><category term="ps4" /><category term="breakpoint" /><category term="apex-legends" /><category term="borderlands-3" /><category term="call-of-duty" /><category term="modern-warfare" /><category term="rainbow-six-siege" /><summary type="html">Welcome to our first Dads Gaming “What we played”, a new monthly segment where we share what our community has been playing. This month we got a special treat in Rainbow Six Siege, explored Aurora Island in Ghost Recon Breakpoint, dived into Season 3 of Apex Legends, spoiled by the guns in the King of Looter Shooters: Borderlands 3, and cross-played in Call of Duty Modern Warfare.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2020-01-27.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sign-ups for the Dads Gaming MLB The Show 19 Tournament</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events/2019/01/08/dadsgaming-mlb-the-show-19-tournament/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sign-ups for the Dads Gaming MLB The Show 19 Tournament" /><published>2019-01-08T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2019-01-08T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events/2019/01/08/dadsgaming-mlb-the-show-19-tournament</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events/2019/01/08/dadsgaming-mlb-the-show-19-tournament/">&lt;p&gt;Our second offline Dads Gaming MLB The Show 19 Tournament returns! Sign-ups are live now! Deadline is 4/15.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full details are posted in our Discord Chat Server. Access to discord is available after registration: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dadsgaming.com/register/&quot;&gt;http://dadsgaming.com/register/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>renovatio_42</name></author><category term="[&quot;events&quot;]" /><category term="baseball" /><category term="ps4" /><category term="sports" /><summary type="html">Our second offline Dads Gaming MLB The Show 19 Tournament returns! Sign-ups are live now! Deadline is 4/15.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2019-01-08.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dads Gaming Community Game Night Event: Call of Duty Black Ops 4</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events/2018/10/16/dadsgaming-game-night-event-call-of-duty-black-ops-4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dads Gaming Community Game Night Event: Call of Duty Black Ops 4" /><published>2018-10-16T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-10-16T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events/2018/10/16/dadsgaming-game-night-event-call-of-duty-black-ops-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events/2018/10/16/dadsgaming-game-night-event-call-of-duty-black-ops-4/">&lt;p&gt;This Saturday night, join us for our Dads Gaming Community Game Night on Call of Duty Black Ops 4! We’ll be playing private matches, multiplayer, and BlackOut games on both PS4 and Xbox One! More info in our discord chat server. &lt;a href=&quot;http://dadsgaming.com/register/&quot;&gt;Register using this link for an invite to our discord server&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to Call of Duty Black Ops 4, checkout our &lt;a href=&quot;http://dadsgaming.com/games/2018/10/03/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops-4-Blackout-Day-1-Strategy/&quot;&gt;Blackout Day 1 Strategy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://dadsgaming.com/games/2018/10/03/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops-4-Beta-Debriefing/&quot;&gt;Debriefing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/search/ref=as_li_qf_sp_sr_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=dadsgamingus-20&amp;amp;keywords=call of duty black ops 4&amp;amp;index=aps&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;linkCode=xm2&amp;amp;linkId=c832e42d66f3974954dcbca032e308e4&quot;&gt;Buy Call of Duty Black Ops 4 for PC, PS4, and Xbox One using our Amazon Affiliate Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>renovatio_42</name></author><category term="[&quot;events&quot;]" /><category term="activision" /><category term="black-ops-4" /><category term="call-of-duty" /><category term="ps4" /><category term="xbox-one" /><summary type="html">This Saturday night, join us for our Dads Gaming Community Game Night on Call of Duty Black Ops 4! We’ll be playing private matches, multiplayer, and BlackOut games on both PS4 and Xbox One! More info in our discord chat server. Register using this link for an invite to our discord server</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2018-10-16.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Call of Duty Black Ops 4 Beta Debrief</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/10/03/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops-4-Beta-Debriefing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Call of Duty Black Ops 4 Beta Debrief" /><published>2018-10-03T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-10-03T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2018/10/03/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops-4-Beta-Debriefing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/10/03/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops-4-Beta-Debriefing/">&lt;p&gt;The closed beta for Call of Duty Black Ops 4 has come to a close, just before the full release on October 12, 2018. We’re looking back on: Multiplayer and new Battle Royale Mode, called Black Out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;multiplayer&quot;&gt;Multiplayer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-flickr-embed=&quot;true&quot; href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/126304189@N08/30139579797/in/dateposted-public/&quot; title=&quot;call-of-duty-black-ops-4-private-beta.jpg.optimal&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1918/30139579797_70f4bfc2a1_c.jpg&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;445&quot; alt=&quot;call-of-duty-black-ops-4-private-beta.jpg.optimal&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Favorite COD’s of all time in no particular order are COD2, COD4, MW2, Blops1-2, and WWII. Favorite non-COD would be TF2.
With that being said - based on playing the beta for several hours over the weekend and making it to level 32, I actually found the game to be quite enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;on-the-positive-side&quot;&gt;On the positive side&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I really liked the feel and sound of the guns&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Getting kills is extremely satisfying&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The increased health and longer TTK made gunfights more interesting and fun IMHO&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I like the stem shot, it adds a decision point in a gun fight…. reload or heal.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The variety of loadout options and specialist abilities gives you lots of combinations to experiment with to match your play style&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nades must be used very strategically as they are few and far between now&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Boots on the ground&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;on-the-negative-side&quot;&gt;On the negative side&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Regardless if you get the jump and catch the enemy by surprise, you will definitely die when outnumbered in a gun fight&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No default nades (frag, flashbang, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Frag nade does not unlock until level 29&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There does not appear to be a way to combine both a frag and a flashbang in your loadout&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For me, not having default nades of any kind is really strange for a COD game. It also hurts my particular playstyle as I have honed my skills over - the years with throwing a nade into the perfect location at the perfect time. On the flipside, everybody that has complained about “nade spam” over - the years should be extremely happy now as this game is focused on the gun on gun engagements.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Some respawn location issues, but it’s a beta and not that big of a deal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are technical and game specific, however my greatest concern with this game is that I won’t have a core group of guys to play with. As I feared, this was a real problem in the beta when playing dom/hardpoint as I routinely found myself all alone trying to cap the B flag… even at the starting of the match!!!! Not surprisingly I would get killed 99% of the time before capping the flag which was extremely frustrating! So I don’t know if I have the stomach to play this game alone as not many (if any) of my friends are interested in this game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, on the other hand I’m not sure I want to continuing playing WWII for another year as that game feels a little boring, repetitive, and simplistic compared to BO4. I still love WWII, but unlocking new stuff and exploring new loadouts and game modes will probably push me to get BO4. I suspect that after playing WWII for the next month and half I will be ready to jump ship and play something new in October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;black-out&quot;&gt;Black Out&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-flickr-embed=&quot;true&quot; href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/126304189@N08/43263970650/in/dateposted-public/&quot; title=&quot;cod-blackout&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1945/43263970650_1934abc9e2_c.jpg&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; alt=&quot;cod-blackout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I really enjoyed the MP beta a few weeks back (see review here), I wasn’t even excited for the Blackout mode as I’m not a Battle Royale player.  I never tried PUBG and only played 2 games of Fortnite.  As somebody that typically only likes game modes that have respawns (domination, hard point, kill confirmed, deathmatch, etc) I really didn’t care about this new Blackout mode.  However, this all changed when they dropped the first gameplay trailer and all of a sudden it caught my attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what do I think after playing the beta for nearly 7 hours of the weekend?  I really like it!  Even though I died right out of the gate on several occasions and had difficulty managing the inventory controls, I found myself jonesing to play all weekend!  So what is it about this game that appeals to me… and many others apparently?  Well, I think it’s not only the fresh take on battle royale with COD guns and gameplay but there are a lot of little details that blend together to make an awesome immersive environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, the sights and sounds are fantastic.  From the sound of the cargo plane flying overhead to the streamers coming off its wingtips, it just sounds and looks great!  The sound of the circle collapsing and running over all the different ground elements is just perfect.  And seeing old maps gives a sense of serious nostalgia for those of us that burned hundreds of hours in MP running around those iconic locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also really like finding all of the various gear and looting dead players backpacks.  And getting a kill in this game is extremely satisfying as they are pretty hard to come by.  When playing MP you can get 3-4 kills right out of the gate, but in this game getting 3 kills can sometimes take a couple games.  And while I typically do not like that style gameplay (aka search and destroy) I didn’t mind it while playing blackout.  I also only won two games, one of which I was dead in my squad so that wasn’t exactly satisfying but the other was in a close quarter duo match where both my partner and I were the last team standing!  That felt great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for my big ticket takeaways, I don’t really have “dislikes” but rather I have several things I am going to have to master if I want to get good at this game:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On initial drop, steer clear of any structures that have several other parachutes landing near them.  While you may be tempted to land there in hopes of getting quick kills, if you aren’t the first guy to find a gun you are SCREWED!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;After you land, find a gun IMMEDIATELY!  I died at least 3-4 times when I couldn’t find a gun before the other guys in the building.  I spent too much time picking up all the other stuff along the way instead of strictly looking for a gun.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Get comfortable with the nerve racking nature of this game type.  As somebody who is used to respawns, only having one life really gets my blood pumping as the match progresses.  So I need to stay calm and keep relaxed.  I had a solo match last night and was down to the last couple guys, but when I was laying prone and looking through my inventory I heard a guy nearby and panicked.  I scrambled to close my inventory menu and inadvertently clicked jump and hopped up in the air.  He then shot me and I died with some serious frustration.  I watched the killcam and sure enough my panic jump caught his attention.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Become proficient with the inventory navigation and how/when to use perks.  This will apply to everyone of course, but I feel this is definitely a key area to master.  Knowing when and where to use certain perks and equipment will be the difference between winning and losing in this game.  Along those lines, it would be really nice if they add some kind of practice zone or private match option where you can get familiar with everything without having to learn in game.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, those are the key takeaways for me.  I know I really like this game as I dreamed about it on both Friday and Saturday night - ha!  One dream was that I kept seeing and hearing the circle collapse around me and the other dream was swapping through all of my attachments and guns.  So between my enjoyment of both the MP and blackout, I am definitely picking this game up on October 12!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/search/ref=as_li_qf_sp_sr_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=dadsgamingus-20&amp;amp;keywords=call of duty black ops 4&amp;amp;index=aps&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;linkCode=xm2&amp;amp;linkId=c832e42d66f3974954dcbca032e308e4&quot;&gt;Buy Call of Duty Black Ops 4 for PC, PS4, and Xbox One using our Amazon Affiliate Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sgtpayback</name></author><category term="[&quot;games&quot;]" /><category term="activision" /><category term="beta" /><category term="black-ops-4" /><category term="call-of-duty" /><category term="take-aways" /><summary type="html">The closed beta for Call of Duty Black Ops 4 has come to a close, just before the full release on October 12, 2018. We’re looking back on: Multiplayer and new Battle Royale Mode, called Black Out.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2018-10-03.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Call of Duty Black Ops 4 Blackout: Day 1 Strategy</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/10/03/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops-4-Blackout-Day-1-Strategy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Call of Duty Black Ops 4 Blackout: Day 1 Strategy" /><published>2018-10-03T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-10-03T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2018/10/03/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops-4-Blackout-Day-1-Strategy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/10/03/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops-4-Blackout-Day-1-Strategy/">&lt;p&gt;As a decades long MP veteran I don’t really need to talk shop regarding Dom, TDM, etc.  However…. Blackout (battle royale) is a whole new experience for me and probably many of you also.  So the purpose of this thread is to try and layout as much strategy and tips and tricks as we can for launch day.  I anticipate that our strategy and approach to this game will change over time as we get better, but I hope this guide can at least get us pointed in the right direction on day one. Please add your own suggestions and comments and I will update the map and info as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This initial guide is based on my limited time with the beta which produced rather unimpressive stats:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Time: 6 hr 51 min&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Level: 6&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Games:  47&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wins: 2 (only alive for 1)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Top 5: 11 times&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kills: 43&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deaths: 44&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the key areas to discuss:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Map &amp;amp; Drop Locations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weapons&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perks &amp;amp; Equipment&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;General Tips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;map--drop-locations&quot;&gt;Map &amp;amp; Drop Locations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the major locations have plenty of weapons.  However, dropping to those locations is an extremely risky endeavor.  If you don’t find a weapon first, your dead.  In my case, I was on the short end of the stick more times than not when playing the beta.  So the purpose of this map is to highlight possible alternative landing zones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;drop-zone-map&quot;&gt;Drop Zone Map&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-flickr-embed=&quot;true&quot; href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/126304189@N08/44356536394/in/dateposted-public/&quot; title=&quot;blackout-map&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1933/44356536394_9e9825b150_c.jpg&quot; width=&quot;790&quot; height=&quot;800&quot; alt=&quot;blackout-map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;GREEN ZONES&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt; &lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;(A) Estates East&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Weapons can be found in the house and on the driveway, usually people land in the main estates but you might find a few others here as well.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;(B) Hydro West&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Plenty of weapons and gear in multiple rooms.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;(C) Hillside&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Each house typically has a weapon.  This was my winning location when playing close quarters duos.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;(D) Nuketown Bunkers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Even though I had heard about this, I never bothered to find it when playing the beta.  Wow… that was a mistake!  After the beta I watched some videos on this area and not only does it look really cool, but there are a TON of great weapons and gear in this spot.  I’m sure you can count on finding others landing here, but it’s worth a try as the payoff could be huge.  They key is knowing where the openings (hatches) are to the bunker. Below are the four ways to get into the bunker along with a detailed tour.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.screencast.com/t/p40IgohEMuT8&quot;&gt;Map - Bunker Hatch Locations&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZY_E4QxiwAA&quot;&gt;YouTube - Gameplay Tour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;(E) Rivertown South&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;There are plenty of houses with loot south of Rivertown.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;BLUE ZONES&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;These look like possible good drop locations.  Anybody drop here during the beta?  Other potential spots?&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;landing-tips-and-tricks&quot;&gt;Landing Tips and Tricks&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across this video today which does a good job of showing you how to drop properly. No wonder I was getting to spots later than others as I was waiting until the helicopter was nearly directly above the spot I wanted to land before jumping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vNbbe_xrtoc&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;weapons&quot;&gt;Weapons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some good starting point resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Videos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z7mDS-kJbno&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UugGAYP4nGg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Articles
https://gameranx.com/features/id/161533/article/black-ops-4-blackout-here-are-the-best-weapons-to-use-in-any-situation-greatest-guns-guide/
https://www.pcgamesn.com/call-of-duty-black-ops-4/blackout-weapons-best-guns
https://www.ign.com/wikis/call-of-duty-black-ops-4/The_Best_Weapons_To_Use_In_Blackout
https://www.dexerto.com/call-of-duty/what-are-the-best-guns-in-the-call-of-duty-blackout-beta-162923&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;perks--equipment&quot;&gt;Perks &amp;amp; Equipment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some good starting point resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Videos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/HLmtbluiOjQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/L5PzF8e2pgs&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iCwJ5_ImgvQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Articles
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/wikis/call-of-duty-black-ops-4/How_Blackout_Perks_Work&quot;&gt;How Blackout Perks Work&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://progameguides.com/call-of-duty/cod-guides/call-of-duty-blackout-perks-list/&quot;&gt;Blackout Perks List&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;general-tips&quot;&gt;General Tips&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On initial drop, if possible steer clear of any structures that have several other parachutes landing near them.  While you may be tempted to land there in hopes of getting quick kills, if you aren’t the first guy to find a gun you are SCREWED!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;After you land, find a gun IMMEDIATELY!  I died at least 3-4 times when I couldn’t find a gun before the other guys in the building.  I spent too much time picking up all the other stuff along the way instead of strictly looking for a gun.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Get comfortable with the nerve racking nature of this game type.  As somebody who is used to respawns, only having one life really gets my blood pumping as the match progresses.  So we need to stay calm and keep relaxed.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Become proficient with the inventory navigation and how/when to use perks.  This will apply to everyone of course, but I feel this is definitely a key area to master.  Knowing when and where to use certain perks and equipment will be the difference between winning and losing in this game.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/search/ref=as_li_qf_sp_sr_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=dadsgamingus-20&amp;amp;keywords=call of duty black ops 4&amp;amp;index=aps&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;linkCode=xm2&amp;amp;linkId=c832e42d66f3974954dcbca032e308e4&quot;&gt;Buy Call of Duty Black Ops 4 for PC, PS4, and Xbox One using our Amazon Affiliate Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sgtpayback</name></author><category term="[&quot;games&quot;]" /><category term="activision" /><category term="beta" /><category term="black-ops-4" /><category term="call-of-duty" /><category term="take-aways" /><summary type="html">As a decades long MP veteran I don’t really need to talk shop regarding Dom, TDM, etc. However…. Blackout (battle royale) is a whole new experience for me and probably many of you also. So the purpose of this thread is to try and layout as much strategy and tips and tricks as we can for launch day. I anticipate that our strategy and approach to this game will change over time as we get better, but I hope this guide can at least get us pointed in the right direction on day one. Please add your own suggestions and comments and I will update the map and info as needed.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2018-10-03a.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Founder Renovatio 42 and DadsGaming Year 4</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/07/30/founder-experience-dads-gaming-year-4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Founder Renovatio 42 and DadsGaming Year 4" /><published>2018-07-30T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-07-30T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2018/07/30/founder-experience-dads-gaming-year-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/07/30/founder-experience-dads-gaming-year-4/">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ProC-kURGBA&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>renovatio_42</name></author><category term="[&quot;games&quot;]" /><category term="Member" /><category term="Spotlight" /><category term="turns-4" /><category term="youtube" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2018-07-30.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Member JohnnyVonRotten and DadsGaming Year 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/06/16/member-experience-dads-gaming-year-3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Member JohnnyVonRotten and DadsGaming Year 3" /><published>2018-06-16T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-06-16T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2018/06/16/member-experience-dads-gaming-year-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/06/16/member-experience-dads-gaming-year-3/">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yrUR_k9NmlI&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>renovatio_42</name></author><category term="[&quot;games&quot;]" /><category term="Member" /><category term="Spotlight" /><category term="turns-3" /><category term="youtube" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2018-06-16.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Operation Supply Drop Charity Event with Dads Gaming</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events/2018/05/25/operation-supply-drop-charity-event-with-dads-gaming/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Operation Supply Drop Charity Event with Dads Gaming" /><published>2018-05-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-05-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events/2018/05/25/operation-supply-drop-charity-event-with-dads-gaming</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events/2018/05/25/operation-supply-drop-charity-event-with-dads-gaming/">&lt;p&gt;Dads Gaming has had the pleasure of working with Operation Supply Drop for the last three years in different capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We began three years ago with a week long stream that spanned Sunday to Saturday. To see the amount of growth from that time to now in both the OSD organization and our involvement stuns this writer. We have raised over $1k through donations and T-Shirts. Even some our own Dad’s Gaming members who are also veterans have seen their lives impacted by working with OSD in their own areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To show some of the incredible work that OSD has been doing this last year look no further because we have some stories for you to check out. In April of this year they sent a deployment overseas to troops from Lexington, KY (Go Cats) and Austin Texas. Supplies for this drop came from Starbucks, Microsoft, Disgruntled Decks, USAA, GAEMS and other OSD partners. In March they dropped a payload for the 10th Mountain Troops and a multinational conglomerate of forces. Just days before this, the 3/2 Calvary Regiment deployed to Poland received a drop as well. Endeavors like these take time and money. Many of our members have no time to go and participate in these drops themselves, but have the finances to aid others in making this happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-flickr-embed=&quot;true&quot; href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/126304189@N08/42296081992/in/dateposted-public/&quot; title=&quot;We are OSD (3)&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1756/42296081992_66bb8f57fd_z.jpg&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; alt=&quot;We are OSD (3)&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to know more about OSD Dads Gaming encourages readers to look at &lt;a href=&quot;https://weareosd.org&quot;&gt;weareosd.org&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://dadsgaming.com/tag/operation-supply-drop/&quot;&gt;dadsgaming.com&lt;/a&gt; and read our personal interview with some of their personnel. We hope you will join us in celebrating OSD this weekend and give towards a worthy cause!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;meet-our-stream-team-for-operation-supply-drop-2018&quot;&gt;Meet our Stream Team for Operation Supply Drop 2018&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitch.tv/thedadsgaming/&quot;&gt;twitch.tv/thedadsgaming/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-flickr-embed=&quot;true&quot; href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/126304189@N08/42296081572/in/dateposted-public/&quot; title=&quot;Dads Gaming OSD 2018 Schedule&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1735/42296081572_ebc5a037e8_b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;800&quot; alt=&quot;Dads Gaming OSD 2018 Schedule&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lesgetgaming</name></author><category term="[&quot;events&quot;]" /><category term="charity" /><category term="operation-supply-drop" /><summary type="html">Dads Gaming has had the pleasure of working with Operation Supply Drop for the last three years in different capacities.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2018-05-25.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Member Lesgetgaming and DadsGaming Year 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/05/07/member-experience-dads-gaming-year-3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Member Lesgetgaming and DadsGaming Year 3" /><published>2018-05-07T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-05-07T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2018/05/07/member-experience-dads-gaming-year-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/05/07/member-experience-dads-gaming-year-3/">&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BOMZcRxKDRc&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>renovatio_42</name></author><category term="[&quot;games&quot;]" /><category term="Member" /><category term="Spotlight" /><category term="turns-3" /><category term="youtube" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2018-05-07.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dads Gaming has partnered with Leaptrade!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/04/30/dadsgaming-partnered-with-leaptrade/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dads Gaming has partnered with Leaptrade!" /><published>2018-04-30T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-04-30T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/games/2018/04/30/dadsgaming-partnered-with-leaptrade</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/games/2018/04/30/dadsgaming-partnered-with-leaptrade/">&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to annouce that &lt;a href=&quot;http://dadsgaming.com/&quot;&gt;Dads Gaming&lt;/a&gt; has partnered with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.leaptrade.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Leaptrade&lt;/a&gt;, a platform service that connects people together to complete a trade of a game. Trading games online has never been easier! With Leaptrade, you can trade your game for &lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt; with fellow gamers and there’s no subscription service or listing fees!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Dads Gaming, we strive to partner with mission-driven companies who share our passion and commitment to providing the best gaming experience. Leaptrade is a perfect example: they offer free trading with trade guaranteee and an easy, hassle-free, experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-get-started&quot;&gt;How to get started?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Register yourself: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.leaptrade.com/groups/dadsgaming&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.leaptrade.com/register&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Select &lt;strong&gt;Dads Gaming&lt;/strong&gt; for “How’d you hear about us?”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Post a game that you’d like to trade&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm1.staticflickr.com/903/27925460098_6668da7ae0.jpg&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; height=&quot;238&quot; alt=&quot;leaptrade_partner_reference&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Leaptrade’s trading is only available in the United States&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-join-our-dads-gaming-group-on-leaptrade&quot;&gt;How to join our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.leaptrade.com/groups/dadsgaming&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dads Gaming Group&lt;/a&gt; on Leaptrade?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s super easy! Just follow the steps outlined in the &lt;strong&gt;How to get started&lt;/strong&gt; section&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;bg-warning&quot;&gt;Leaptrade is Dads Gaming's only supported method of trading games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;when-to-use-leaptrade&quot;&gt;When to use Leaptrade?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often is the answer. Do you have a game sitting on the shelf collecting dust? Are looking for a used game, in good condition without the frustration and disappointment?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Play more - save time with a hassle-free exprience trading your used games. No more getting low-balled at the brick-and-mortor retailers. Forget about the random encounters to meet-up hoping the game you’re getting is in good condition.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Worry-free - every trade made on Leaptrade’s website is backed by their trade protection&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Games, games, and more games! - For all of these systems and more: Xbox One, PS4, PC, Xbox 360, PS3, Original Xbox, PSP, PS2, PS1, and even retro game systems like Atari, Sega Genesis, Nintendo NES, Gameboy Advance&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Just between friends - If another friend or Dads Gaming member finds your game and they’re interested you can adjust the price for a friend-to-friend trade! Remember all trades are free, so everybody wins! &lt;img src=&quot;https://farm1.staticflickr.com/959/41076817404_9bf4902bcb_z.jpg&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;303&quot; alt=&quot;share_disc&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Check out our Infographic!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm1.staticflickr.com/904/26925868777_1c80818955_o.png&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;2000&quot; alt=&quot;Leaptrade Infographic&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>renovatio_42</name></author><category term="[&quot;games&quot;]" /><category term="leaptrade" /><category term="trade-your-games" /><summary type="html">We are pleased to annouce that Dads Gaming has partnered with Leaptrade, a platform service that connects people together to complete a trade of a game. Trading games online has never been easier! With Leaptrade, you can trade your game for FREE with fellow gamers and there’s no subscription service or listing fees!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/2018-04-30.png" /></entry></feed>